A Guide to the American Public Transportation Association Collection
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- American Public Transportation Association Collection
  - National League of Cities (Box Box 71)
  - National League of Cities (Box Box 71)
  - National League of Cities (Box Box 71)
  - National League of Cities (Box Box 71)
  - Canadian Transit Association-Annual Meetings (Box Box 71)
  - National League of Cities (Box Box 71)
  - TELEPHONE DISPATCH (Box Box 72)
  - TELEPHONE DISPATCH (Box Box 72)
  - AFFIRMATIVE REPLIES (Box Box 72)
  - REPORTS (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - PASSENGER (Box Box 72)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULES (Box Box 72)
  - REPLIES/REGULATIONS (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - PASSENGER (Box Box 72)
  - INFORMATION REPORT (Box Box 72)
  - PASSENGERS (Box Box 72)
  - REPLIES (Box Box 72)
  - Replies (Box Box 72)
  - SUMMARIES (Box Box 72)
  - REGULATIONS (Box Box 72)
  - COMMUNICATIONS (Box Box 72)
  - SAFETY TEST (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - SCHEDULING (Box Box 72)
  - ONE MAN CAR OPERATION (Box Box 72)
  - Interurban Transportation (Box Box 72)
  - Interurban Cars Selected Articles May, 1947 (Box Box 72)
  - 520.04 Origin-Destination Survey (Box Box 72)
  - 520.021 Hubodometers, Odometers-Milage (Box Box 72)
  - 520.02 Vehicle Miles (Box Box 72)
  - Passenger Revenue-Vehicle Miles 1946-1956 (Box Box 72)
  - 520.003 Harrisburg, PA Opinion Research Survey (Box Box 72)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 073.1 GENERAL (Box Box 73)
  - 012.303 BUS OPERATORS WORK HOURS-AFFIRMATIVE REPLIES (Box Box 74)
  - 012.303 BUS OPERATORS WORK HOURS-NEGATIVE REPLIES (Box Box 74)
  - 013 FLSA (Box Box 74)
  - 013 FAIR LABOR STANDARDS ACT (Box Box 74)
  - 013.16 ARBITRATION AWARDS (Box Box 74)
  - 013 TRANSIT STRIKES (Box Box 74)
  - 013.18 TRANSIT STRIKES (Box Box 74)
  - BUS DOWN REPORT (Box Box 74)
  - REPLIES TO COMM MEMBERS RE HANDLING OF PARTS (Box Box 74)
  - MOTOR COACH SUBSTITUTE MATERIALS (Box Box 74)
  - 027.141 GLAZING MATERIALS (Box Box 74)
  - 027.141 GLAZING MATERIALS (Box Box 74)
  - 027.141 GLAZING MATERIALS (Box Box 74)
  - 071.2 VANDALISM AND PASSENGER SECURITY (Box Box 74)
  - 071.3 RIOTS (Box Box 74)
  - 608.32 VANDALISM (Box Box 74)
  - 071.2 CRIME AND VANDALISM (Box Box 74)
  - 073 FINANCES (Box Box 74)
  - SPECIAL REPORT-Relief Actions from taxes and imposts (Box Box 74)
  - URBAN BUS DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 75)
  - URBAN MOTOR COACH DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 75)
  - URBAN MOTOR COACH DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES-PURCHASE AND STORE DIVISION Oct 1935 to date (Box Box 75)
  - (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES-PURCHASE AND STORES DIVISION Oct 1935 - date (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES-PURCHASE AND STORES DIVISION Oct 1935-date (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES-PURCHASE AND STORES DIVISION Oct 1935 - date (Box Box 75)
  - 874.433 COMMITTEE ON PURCHASING PRACTICES (BATTERIES) (Box Box 75)
  - 870 SUBSTITUTE MATERIALS VALUE ANALYSIS (Box Box 75)
  - 873 SUBSTITUTE MATERIALS AND VALUE ANALYSIS (Box Box 75)
  - PM AND M COMMITTEE 1972-1973 (Box Box 75)
  - 873.1 NOMINATING COMMITTEE P & S (Box Box 75)
  - 873.1 P & S DIVISION - CHANGE OF NAME (Box Box 75)
  - 873.1 MID-YEAR MEETING 1969 CHICAGO-ILLINOIS 4-8-1969 (Box Box 75)
  - 874.03 PROGRAMS FORE REGIONAL MEETINGS (Box Box 75)
  - 874.433 COMM. ON PROBLEMS OF AUTOMATION IN P & S (Box Box 75)
  - P & M ADMIN. COMMITTEE 11-19-1969 (Box Box 75)
  - PURCHASE AND MATERIALS MGMT DIVN Meeting Programs (Box Box 75)
  - P.M.M. COMMITTEE (Box Box 75)
  - GENERAL - PURCHASE & STORES ADMINISTRATIVE COMM. (Box Box 75)
  - MECHANICAL DIVISION ADMIN COMMITTEE MINUTES Dec 1943 (Box Box 75)
  - MECHANICAL DIVISION ADMIN COMMITTEE MINUTES Dec 1943 (Box Box 75)
  - MECHANICAL DIVISION Dec 2,1970 (Box Box 75)
  - MECH. DIV. ADMINIS. COMM. JANUARY 21 (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES OF EXEC. COMM. MEETINGS OF THE BUS DIVISION (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES OF EXEC. COMM. MEETINGS OF THE BUS DIVISION (Box Box 75)
  - MINUTES OF EXEC. COMM. MEETINGS OF THE BUS DIVISION (Box Box 75)
  - ATA BUS DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 75)
  - ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON MOTOR COACHES (Box Box 75)
  - 884.24 ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 75)
  - 885.1 COMM. ON STANDARDS AND MEASUREMENTS (Box Box 75)
  - 885.2 COMM. ON COMPARATIVE POWER SOURCES (Box Box 75)
  - 855.3 COMM. ON. FUELS, LUBS AND ADDITIVES (Box Box 75)
  - 885.4 COMMITTEE ON APPURTENANCES (Box Box 75)
  - 582.2 CLAIMS TRANSIT COMPANIES (Box Box 76)
  - 582.2 CLAIMS STATS. TRANSIT COMPANIES (Box Box 76)
  - 582.203 CLAIMS SETTLEMENT COSTS (Box Box 76)
  - 582.5 CLAIMS AND SUITS STATISTICS May 1974 (Box Box 76)
  - 582.52 TRANSIT COS SUITS AND CLAIMS (Box Box 76)
  - 582.520.1 WITNESSES (Box Box 76)
  - 582.520 INFORMATION RE. MAIL QUESTIONARIES TO WITNESSES (Box Box 76)
  - 582.521.2 ACCIDENT - SUDDEN ILLNESS OF OPERATORS (Box Box 76)
  - 582.523 MOTOR BUS CLAIMS DIVISION (Box Box 76)
  - 583.206 SELF INSURED TRANSIT COMPANIES June 3, 1964 (Box Box 76)
  - 582.5231 CLAIMS-LOSS OF USE - VEHICLES UNDER REPAIR (Box Box 76)
  - INSURANCE AND SAFETY (Box Box 76)
  - 583.206 TRANSIT COMPANIES SELF INSURANCE (Box Box 76)
  - 583.206.1 RESERVES FOR INJURIES (Box Box 76)
  - 600.03 BIBLIOGRAPHY (Box Box 76)
  - 600.1 URBAN TRAFFIC (Box Box 76)
  - 600.1 NATIONAL COMM. ON URBAN TRANSPORTATION (Box Box 76)
  - URBAN TRANSIT IMPROVEMENTS (Box Box 76)
  - URBAN TRANSIT IMPROVEMENTS - Subsidized fares (Box Box 76)
  - 600.138.21 EXCLUSIVE BUS LANES (Box Box 76)
  - 600.138.21 EXCLUSIVE BUS LANES (Box Box 76)
  - 600.151.153 URBAN TRANSIT (Box Box 76)
  - 600.421 BUS OPERATIONS (Box Box 76)
  - 600.423 STATISTICS (Box Box 76)
  - 602 ADVERTISING GENERAL (Box Box 76)
  - 602.32 ADVERTISING ON SCHEDULES (Box Box 76)
  - 602.7 ADVERTISING REVENUE (Box Box 76)
  - 415.1363 VENDING MACHINES ON MOTOR BUSES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.137.3 MIRRORS ON BUSES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.014 PUPIL TRANSPORTATION SAFETY (Box Box 77)
  - 415.145 DESTINATION SIGNS, ROUTE SIGNS, NUMBER (Box Box 77)
  - 415.15 WINDOWS (Box Box 77)
  - 415.16 CENTER-EXIT PUSH TYPE DOORS (Box Box 77)
  - 415.161 EMERGENCY DOORS (Box Box 77)
  - 415.172 VENTILATION, AIR-PURIFICATION (Box Box 77)
  - 415.193 SPEEDOMETERS (Box Box 77)
  - 415.28 BRAKES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.281 JACOBS BRAKE (Box Box 77)
  - 415.286 AIR BRAKES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.286 AIR BRAKES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.286 L.W. BARDSLEY (Box Box 77)
  - 415.293 ORIGINAL REPLIES AND ANALYSIS (Box Box 77)
  - 415.293 TIRES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.293 TIRES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.293 TIRES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.313 BUS ENGINE FUEL EXHAUST (Box Box 77)
  - 415.35 BUS ENGINE FUEL EXHAUST (Box Box 77)
  - 415.284 AUTOMATIC SLACK ADJUSTER/AUTOMATIC DRAIN VALVES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.43 BATTERIES (Box Box 77)
  - 415.43 BATTERIES (Box Box 78)
  - 415.511 DIESEL FUEL SHORTAGE (Box Box 78)
  - 415.513 USE OF LIQUEFIED PETROLEUM GAS AS MOTOR FUEL (Box Box 78)
  - 415.73 OIL FILTERS (Box Box 78)
  - 093.A.00 AUTOMOBILES FOR OFFICIALS (Box Box 78)
  - 874.1 PURCHASE AND RENTAL OF BATTERIES (Box Box 79)
  - 874 HANDLING OF NEW AND REPAIRED UNITS (Box Box 79)
  - 874.3 MATERIAL CLASSIFICATION GUIDE (Box Box 79)
  - 874.3 MATERIAL CLASSIFICATION GUIDE (Box Box 79)
  - 874.33 1954 INITIAL STOCKING AND MATERIAL RETURN POLICY (Box Box 79)
  - 874.42 SPECIFICATIONS (Box Box 79)
  - 874.431 TIRES - 1967 (Box Box 79)
  - 874.431 TIRES - 1967 (Box Box 79)
  - 874.431 TIRES, REPORT OF SUB-COMMITTEE (1957) (Box Box 79)
  - 884 BETTER MAINTENANCE METHODS - LOWER COSTS (Box Box 79)
  - 884 MARCH 1954 USE OF TIRE CHAINS ON BUSINESS (Box Box 79)
  - 884 URBAN MOTOR COACH DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 79)
  - 884 URBAN MOTOR COACH DESIGN OBJECTIVES (Box Box 79)
  - 874.432 P & S COMMITTEE ON PROBLEMS OF AUTOMATION (Box Box 79)
  - 874.432 FUELS AND LUBRICANTS (Box Box 79)
  - 874.433 BATTERIES (Box Box 79)
  - 874.83 COMMITTEE ON SERVICES FOR PROFIT (Box Box 79)
  - 874.911 OCT 1959 COOPERATION WITH MFR.DIVN (Box Box 79)
  - 884.21 URBAN COACH OBJECTIVES (Box Box 79)
  - 884.28 BRAKE NOISE (Box Box 79)
  - 884.28 BRAKE SEQUEAL ELIMINATION REPLIES (Box Box 79)
  - 894 PUBLIC RELATIONS MANUAL (Box Box 79)
  - 884 REPLIES ON THE HANDLING OF NEW AND REPAIRED UNITS (Box Box 79)
  - 884 March 17th, 1965 REGROOVING OF TIRES (Box Box 79)
  - 884.24 TROLLEY COACH OBJECTIVE (Box Box 79)
  - 252.083 CLASSIFICATION ACCOUNTS (Box Box 79)
  - 252.083 CLASSIFICATION ACCOUNTS (Box Box 79)
  - 252.083 CLASSIFICATION OF ACCOUNTS (Box Box 79)
  - 252.1102 COST ACCOUNTING (Box Box 79)
  - 300.4 GENERAL (Box Box 79)
  - 300.4 NOW (Box Box 79)
  - 300.33 STEEL IN RAPID TRANSIT SYSTEMS/ELEVATED STRUCTURES (Box Box 79)
  - REPORT OF THE COMMITTEE ON STD CLASSIFICATION OF ACTS March 21, 1946 (Box Box 79)
  - QUESTIONS OF DEVELOPING NEW CLASSIFICATION OF ACCOUNTS FOR TRANSIT COMPANIES Feb, 1956 (Box Box 79)
  - 844.3 1954 REPORT (Box Box 80)
  - 844.3 FORM OF DERAILMENTS (Box Box 80)
  - P4-47 844.4-7 CATENARY OVERHEAD CONSTRUCTION (Box Box 80)
  - P1-49 844.4-1 CURRENT COLLECTION EQUIPMENT (Box Box 80)
  - P1-56 844.4-1 CONVERSION OF ST CAR ELEC. LINE FACILITIES, ETC. (Box Box 80)
  - RECTIFIERS (Box Box 80)
  - TROLLEY COACH OVERHEAD Installation Cost (Box Box 80)
  - USE OF CARBON INSERT SHOE COLLECTORS ON STREET CARS (Box Box 80)
  - TROLLEY WIRE WEAR AND BREAKS LINE MAINTENANCE PERFORMANCE (Box Box 80)
  - REPORT-TROLLEY COACH POWER DISTRIBUTION SYSTEMS (Box Box 80)
  - ELECTRIC TRACK-SWITCH DEVICES (Box Box 80)
  - SPECIF> FOR TUBULAR STEELS POLES for Electric Line Construction (Box Box 80)
  - RAPID TRANSIT WAY AND STRUCTURES COMMITTEE (Box Box 80)
  - ENGINEERING MANUAL SECTION (Box Box 80)
  - ENGINEERING MANUAL SECTION (Box Box 80)
  - TRANSIT PARS (Box Box 80)
  - AMERICAN ASSOCIATION (Box Box 80)
  - ENGINEERING ASSOCIATION/MANUAL SECTIONS (Box Box 80)
  - OPERATING PLAN (Box Box 80)
  - CURRENT "E" MANUAL SECTIONS (Box Box 80)
  - REPLIES TO SPECIAL INQUIRY (Box Box 80)
  - COMMITTEE ON SCHEDULING (Box Box 80)
  - COMMITTEE ON SCHEDULING OPERATIONS DIVISION (Box Box 80)
  - HEADWAY RECORDERS (Box Box 80)
  - OPERATIONS DIVISION (Box Box 80)
  - FARE STRUCTURES (Box Box 80)
  - PROJECT FARE TASK I REPORT (Box Box 81)
  - PROJECT FARE TASK II REPORT (Box Box 81)
  - PROJECT FARE TASK V Industry Control Board Meeting (Box Box 81)
  - TRANSIT INDUSTRY REPORTING CAPABILITY SURVEY (Box Box 81)
  - UMTA FARE PROJECT (Box Box 81)
  - PUBLIC RELATIONS PRACTICES (Box Box 82)
  - A.T.A. LIBRARY FILE PUBLIC RELATIONS PRACTICES (Box Box 82)
  - 080 PUBLIC RELATIONS (Box Box 82)
  - 080.1 TRANSIT ADVERTISING (Box Box 82)
  - 080.1 TRANSIT ADVERTISING (Box Box 82)
  - 080.101 TRANSIT ADVERTISING BUDGETS (Box Box 82)
  - 080.12 HOUSE CARDS - ATA (Box Box 82)
  - 080 FILM CATALOGS (Box Box 82)
  - EXHIBITS OF LATEST NEWSPAPER ADS AND PHOTOS OF SIGNS IN M.T.A. STATIONS (Box Box 82)
  - NEWSPAPERS (Box Box 82)
  - NEWS RELEASES-ARTICLES RE A.T.A. ACTIVITIES (Box Box 82)
  - NEWS RELEASES-ARTICLES RE. ATA ACTIVITIES (Box Box 82)
  - "TAKE ONE" PUBLICITY (Box Box 82)
  - REPLIES TO SPECIAL INQUIRY (Box Box 82)
  - PUBLIC RELATIONS 1972 SAMPLE (Box Box 82)
  - TELEPHONE INFORMATION SERVICE (Box Box 82)
  - TRANSIT INFORMATION-PHONE (Box Box 82)
  - Services to Transit (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1960 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1955 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1963 (Box Box 83)
  - Information Guide (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1965 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1964 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1955 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Jan 1957 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members 1957 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Jan. 1958 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Feb 1964 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members March 1961 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members March 1966 (Box Box 83)
  - Annual Report 171 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Nov. 1946 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Feb. 1963 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Jan 1962 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members April 1962 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Nov.1947 (Box Box 83)
  - Roster of Members Jan 1953 (Box Box 83)
  - 812 Dues Committee 1980 (Box Box 84)
  - Committees-General (Box Box 84)
  - 812.4 Committees-General (Box Box 84)
  - 812.4 Committees-General (Box Box 84)
  - 812.4 Committees-General (Box Box 84)
  - 618.104 AUTOMATIC FARE COLLECTION (Box Box 85)
  - SPECIAL INQUIRY SERVICE 0-791-FARE COLLECTION AND ACCTG. METHODS (Box Box 85)
  - 618.104 AUTOMATIC FARE COLLECTION-COIN HANDLING (Box Box 85)
  - ANNUAL REPORT-Fiscal Year Ended Oct 31, 1974 (Box Box 84)
  - Rental Batteries/Bus Rentals (Box Box 85)
  - 605.1 Effect of Fare Changes (Box Box 85)
  - 605.1 Effect of Fare Changes (Box Box 85)
  - 605.1 Effect of Fare Changes (Box Box 85)
  - 605.1 Effect of Fare Changes (Box Box 85)
  - 605.12 Riding Habit (Box Box 85)
  - 605.2 Passenger Traffic Checks (Box Box 85)
  - Service Charge (Box Box 85)
  - Average Fare (Box Box 85)
  - Charter Rate Regulation (Box Box 85)
  - Tabulations Rate Cases (Box Box 85)
  - Commission and State Powers (Box Box 85)
  - Lost and Found (Box Box 85)
  - Clean Up Promotion (Box Box 85)
  - Summary of Suicide Attempts (Box Box 85)
  - Summary of Suicide Attempts (Box Box 85)
  - "Public Transportation and Needs of the Elderly and Handicapped (Box Box 85)
  - Leonard Ronis speaks regarding Transit Financing (Box Box 85)
  - Smoking on Buses (Box Box 85)
  - Radios, Passenger Use of. (Box Box 85)
  - Music on Vehicles (Box Box 85)
  - Fares General (Box Box 85)
  - Reduction of Fares (Box Box 85)
  - 15 cent fare (Box Box 85)
  - 25 cent to 29 cent fare (Box Box 85)
  - Motor Bus Fares-Long Haul (Box Box 85)
  - Summary of Fare Questionnaire Sept. 1974 (Box Box 85)
  - American Transit Association List of Experiments 12/22/1967 (Box Box 85)
  - Free Transportation (Box Box 85)
  - Special Inquiry Service Free Transportation of Employees (Box Box 85)
  - Children's Fares (Box Box 85)
  - Government and Municipal Emlp. Transportation (Box Box 85)
  - Policemen and Fireman Transportation (Box Box 85)
  - Increasing Basic Fares above 25 cents May 1969 (Box Box 85)
  - Promotional Rates (Box Box 85)
  - TROLLEY COACHES (Box Box 86)
  - POWER TAKE-OFF FOR TRACKLESS TROLLEY CIRCUITS (1947) (Box Box 86)
  - COST OF POWER (Box Box 86)
  - ENERGY CRISIS (Box Box 86)
  - REPLIES TO D.S. ELECTRIC POWER APRIL 16th, 1958 (Box Box 86)
  - ELECTRIC POWER March 17th, 1954 (Box Box 86)
  - ELECTRIC POWER APRIL 1st, 1955 (Box Box 86)
  - ELECTRIC POWER APRIL 1st, 1955 (Box Box 86)
  - ENERGY 56-76 (Box Box 86)
  - ELECTRIC ENERGY CONSUMED BY TRANSIT INDUSTRY (Box Box 86)
  - BATTERIES RENTAL OR PURCHASE (Box Box 86)
  - RELOCATION OF DISTRIBUTION SYSTEM (Box Box 86)
  - REPLIES TO D.S. ELECTRIC POWER March 15th, 1961 (Box Box 86)
  - ELECTROLYSIS AND CORROSION OF CABLE PIPE (Box Box 86)
  - JOINT USE OF POLES (Box Box 86)
  - CONDITIONS OF POLES-TESTING (Box Box 86)
  - TROLLEY BUS XING OVER STM RR, TRK (Box Box 86)
  - TRACK MILEAGE (Box Box 86)
  - TERMINAL LOOPS (Box Box 86)
  - JOINT USE OF TRACKS (Box Box 86)
  - HEATING (Box Box 86)
  - WAITING ROOMS (Box Box 86)
  - ECONOMICS OF SERVICE TO NEW AREAS (Box Box 86)
  - ROUTE-COST ANALYSIS (Box Box 86)
  - ROUTE-COST ANALYSIS (Box Box 86)
  - ROUTE-COST ANALYSIS (Box Box 86)
  - BUS VS STREET CARS (Box Box 86)
  - TROLLEY BUS ANNUAL REPORTS (Box Box 87)
  - RECEIVERSHIP - LIST (Box Box 87)
  - SUBSIDIES-REIMBURSEMENTS-TRANSIT AID BILL (Box Box 87)
  - 1968 AMENDMENTS TO URBAN MASS TRANSPORTATION ACT (1964) (Box Box 87)
  - FEDERAL AID TO TRANSIT (Box Box 87)
  - FEDERAL SUBSIDIES (Box Box 87)
  - GRANTS (Box Box 87)
  - STATEMENT OF BERNARD SHATZKIN (Box Box 87)
  - FEDERAL AID TRANSIT ACTIVITIES (Box Box 87)
  - ATA SUMMARIES (Box Box 87)
  - CAPITAL GRANT PROGRAM (Box Box 87)
  - CAPITAL GRANT PROGRAM (Box Box 87)
  - GENERAL (Box Box 87)
  - TAX RELIEF (Box Box 87)
  - CAPITAL STOCK (Box Box 87)
  - FINANCING GENERAL (Box Box 87)
  - TRANSIT FINANCING (Box Box 87)
  - TRANSIT ECONOMICS AND FINANCE (Box Box 87)
  - FINANCING OF NEW EQUIPMENT (Box Box 87)
  - REVENUE PASSENGER TRAFFIC (Box Box 87)
  - BUS REVENUES (Box Box 87)
  - DEPRECIATION (Box Box 87)
  - RAILROAD OPERATING STATISTICS (Box Box 87)
  - TROLLEY COACH MAINTENANCE COSTS (Box Box 87)
  - TROLLEY COACH DEPRECIATION (Box Box 87)
  - BUS SHELTERS (Box Box 88)
  - BUS SHELTERS (Box Box 88)
  - BUS SHELTERS (Box Box 88)
  - FINANCIAL ASSISTANCE FOR TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 89)
  - FINANCIAL ASSISTANCE FOR TRANSIT SYSTEM (Box Box 89)
  - REPLACEMENT COSTS (Box Box 89)
  - OPERATING BASIS (Box Box 89)
  - DATA PROCESSING (Box Box 89)
  - Reduced fares for Senior Citizens (Box Box 90)
  - Reduced Fares for Senior Citizens (Box Box 90)
  - Reduced Fares for Senior Citizens (Box Box 90)
  - Fares for Senior Citizens (Box Box 90)
  - Fares for Senior Citizens (Box Box 90)
  - Charted Bus Rates (Box Box 90)
  - AUTOMATIC FARE COLLECTION (Box Box 91)
  - SPECIAL INQUIRY SERVICE 0-791- FARE COLLECTION AND ACCTG. METHODS (Box Box 91)
  - AUTOMATIC FARE COLLECTION - COIN HANDLING (Box Box 91)
  - ANNUAL REPORT - FISCAL YEAR ENDED OCT. 31, 1974 (Box Box 91)
  - CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 92)
  - CORRESPONDENCE (Box Box 92)
  - 13C: 1973-1976 (Box Box 92)
  - 13C: 1973-1976 (Box Box 92)
  - 13C: 1973-1976 (Box Box 92)
  - 13C: 1973-1976 (Box Box 92)
  - 13C: 1973-1976 (Box Box 92)
  - National Negotiations (Box Box 92)
  - National Negotiations (Box Box 92)
  - National Negotiations (Box Box 92)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #885 (Box Box 93)
  - 1967 Facts and Figures (Box Box 93)
  - 1969 Facts and Figures (Box Box 93)
  - Hybrid Vehicle Concept (Box Box 93)
  - Commuter Railroad Service (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #880 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #874 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #872 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #867 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #864 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #857 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #852 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #849 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #843 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #842 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #836 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #834 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #832 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #827 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #825 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #819 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #817 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #815 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #809 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #808 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #801 (Box Box 93)
  - Wages and Working Conditions Bulletin #798 (Box Box 93)